{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 30, 'start_offset': 29}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 38, 'start_offset': 33}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 51, 'start_offset': 48}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 92, 'start_offset': 88}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 131, 'start_offset': 126}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 144, 'start_offset': 141}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 153, 'start_offset': 145}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 198, 'start_offset': 161}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 228, 'start_offset': 220}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 292, 'start_offset': 285}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 303, 'start_offset': 298}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 342, 'start_offset': 337}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 738, 'start_offset': 733}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 877, 'start_offset': 863}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "[\nError: Parse error on line 1:\n[House Hearing, 116 C\n-^\nExpecting 'STRING', 'NUMBER', 'NULL', 'TRUE', 'FALSE', '{', '[', ']'\nHouse Hearing, 116 Congress]\n[From the U.S. Government Publishing Office]\n\n\n                  COLORADO'S ROADMAP FOR CLEAN ENERGY\n                     ACTION: LESSONS FROM STATE AND\n                             LOCAL LEADERS\n\n=======================================================================\n\n                                HEARING\n\n                               BEFORE THE\n\n                        SELECT COMMITTEE ON THE\n                             CLIMATE CRISIS\n                        HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES\n\n                     ONE HUNDRED SIXTEENTH CONGRESS\n\n                             FIRST SESSION\n\n                               __________\n\n                              HEARING HELD\n                             AUGUST 1, 2019\n\n                               __________\n\n                            Serial No."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 3, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 137, 'start_offset': 117}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 319, 'start_offset': 317}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 323, 'start_offset': 320}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 355, 'start_offset': 345}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 362, 'start_offset': 358}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 576, 'start_offset': 565}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 586, 'start_offset': 577}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 640, 'start_offset': 633}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 647, 'start_offset': 642}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 661, 'start_offset': 648}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 673, 'start_offset': 663}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 709, 'start_offset': 700}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 727, 'start_offset': 719}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 735, 'start_offset': 729}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 779, 'start_offset': 765}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 791, 'start_offset': 781}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 827, 'start_offset': 819}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 853, 'start_offset': 843}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 885, 'start_offset': 878}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 914, 'start_offset': 906}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 944, 'start_offset': 937}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 967, 'start_offset': 957}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 1009, 'start_offset': 996}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 1031, 'start_offset': 1023}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 1076, 'start_offset': 1064}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 1087, 'start_offset': 1077}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 1097, 'start_offset': 1089}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 1202, 'start_offset': 1197}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 1256, 'start_offset': 1246}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 1485, 'start_offset': 1477}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 1563, 'start_offset': 1560}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '116-8\n\n[GRAPHIC NOT AVAILABLE IN TIFF FORMAT]\n\n                            www.govinfo.gov\n   Printed for the use of the Select Committee on the Climate Crisis\n   \n   \n                               __________\n                               \n\n                    U.S. GOVERNMENT PUBLISHING OFFICE                    \n37-993 PDF                  WASHINGTON : 2019                     \n          \n--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------  \n   \n                 SELECT COMMITTEE ON THE CLIMATE CRISIS\n                     One Hundred Sixteenth Congress\n\n                      KATHY CASTOR, Florida, Chair\nBEN RAY LUJAN, New Mexico            GARRET GRAVES, Louisiana,\nSUZANNE BONAMICI, Oregon               Ranking Member\nJULIA BROWNLEY, California           MORGAN GRIFFITH, Virginia\nJARED HUFFMAN, California            GARY PALMER, Alabama\nA. DONALD McEACHIN, Virginia         BUDDY CARTER, Georgia\nMIKE LEVIN, California               CAROL MILLER, West Virginia\nSEAN CASTEN, Illinois                KELLY ARMSTRONG, North Dakota\nJOE NEGUSE, Colorado\n\n                              ----------                              \n\n                Ana Unruh Cohen, Majority Staff Director\n                  Marty Hall, Minority Staff Director\n                        climatecrisis.house.gov\n                            \n                            \n                            C O N T E N T S\n\n                   STATEMENTS OF MEMBERS OF CONGRESS\n\n                                                                   Page\n Hon.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 12, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 42, 'start_offset': 34}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 71, 'start_offset': 64}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 129, 'start_offset': 77}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 267, 'start_offset': 266}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 272, 'start_offset': 269}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Kathy Castor, a Representative in Congress from the State \n  of Florida, and Chair, Select Committee on the Climate Crisis:\n     Opening Statement...........................................     1\n     Prepared Statement..........................................     3\n Hon.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 14, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 44, 'start_offset': 36}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 75, 'start_offset': 66}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 95, 'start_offset': 81}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 113, 'start_offset': 97}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 211, 'start_offset': 209}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 257, 'start_offset': 256}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Garrett Graves, a Representative in Congress from the State \n  of Louisiana, and Ranking Member, Select Committee on the \n  Climate Crisis:\n     Opening Statement...........................................    16\n\n                            WITNESS: PANEL 1\n\n Hon.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 11, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 40, 'start_offset': 32}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 184, 'start_offset': 183}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 231, 'start_offset': 230}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Jared Polis, Governor, State of Colorado\n     Oral Statement..............................................     7\n     Prepared Statement..........................................     9\n\n                           WITNESSES: PANEL 2\n\n Hon.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 13, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 20, 'start_offset': 15}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 37, 'start_offset': 30}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 47, 'start_offset': 39}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 119, 'start_offset': 117}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 191, 'start_offset': 189}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 196, 'start_offset': 193}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Suzanne Jones, Mayor, City of Boulder, Colorado\n     Oral Statement..............................................    24\n     Prepared Statement..........................................    26\n Hon.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 12, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 19, 'start_offset': 14}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 41, 'start_offset': 29}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 51, 'start_offset': 43}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 123, 'start_offset': 121}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 195, 'start_offset': 193}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 208, 'start_offset': 197}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 233, 'start_offset': 210}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 276, 'start_offset': 248}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 320, 'start_offset': 297}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 365, 'start_offset': 320}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 417, 'start_offset': 415}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 489, 'start_offset': 487}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 503, 'start_offset': 491}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 581, 'start_offset': 556}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 609, 'start_offset': 586}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 675, 'start_offset': 673}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 747, 'start_offset': 745}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 766, 'start_offset': 749}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 823, 'start_offset': 798}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 975, 'start_offset': 973}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 1148, 'start_offset': 1097}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 1181, 'start_offset': 1170}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 1221, 'start_offset': 1215}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Wade Troxell, Mayor, City of Fort Collins, Colorado\n     Oral Statement..............................................    34\n     Prepared Statement..........................................    36\n Cary Weiner, State Energy Specialist and Director, Colorado \n  State University (CSU) Extension and Rural Energy Center \n  Colorado State University\n     Oral Statement..............................................    38\n     Prepared Statement..........................................    39\n Chris Wright, Chief Executive Officer and Executive Chairman, \n  Liberty Oilfield Services and Liberty Resources\n     Oral Statement..............................................    41\n     Prepared Statement..........................................    43\n Heidi VanGenderen, Chief Sustainability Officer, University of \n  Colorado-Boulder\n     Oral Statement..............................................    44\n     Prepared Statement..........................................    46\n\n                       SUBMISSIONS FOR THE RECORD\n\n Report, Source characterization of volatile organic compounds in \n  the Colorado Northern Front Range Metropolitan Area during \n  spring and summer 2015, submitted for the record by Mr. Neguse.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 99, 'start_offset': 83}}, 'display_name': 'LAW'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 236, 'start_offset': 220}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 263, 'start_offset': 238}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 305, 'start_offset': 299}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 336, 'start_offset': 334}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 414, 'start_offset': 411}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "   65\n Report, Process-Based and Regional Source Impact Analysis for \n  FRAPPE and DISCOVER-AQ 2014, submitted for the record by Mr. \n  Neguse.........................................................    65\n Article from CIRES UC-Boulder, ``Accounting for Ozone,'' \n  submitted for the record by Mr. Graves.........................    69\n\n                                APPENDIX\n\n Questions for the Record from Hon."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 12, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 19, 'start_offset': 16}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Kathy Castor to Hon.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 14, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 78, 'start_offset': 76}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 113, 'start_offset': 110}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Jared \n  Polis..........................................................    69\n Questions for the Record from Hon.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 12, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 19, 'start_offset': 16}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Kathy Castor to Hon.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 16, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 80, 'start_offset': 78}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 115, 'start_offset': 112}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Suzanne \n  Jones..........................................................    72\n Questions for the Record from Hon.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 12, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 19, 'start_offset': 16}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Kathy Castor to Hon.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 15, 'start_offset': 8}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 77, 'start_offset': 75}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 112, 'start_offset': 109}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Wade \n  Troxell........................................................    75\n Questions for the Record from Hon.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 12, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 27, 'start_offset': 16}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 35, 'start_offset': 33}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 70, 'start_offset': 67}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Kathy Castor to Cary Weiner..    76\n Questions for the Record from Hon.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 12, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 36, 'start_offset': 16}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 94, 'start_offset': 92}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 108, 'start_offset': 100}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 151, 'start_offset': 144}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 162, 'start_offset': 157}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 202, 'start_offset': 197}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 316, 'start_offset': 308}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 332, 'start_offset': 318}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 422, 'start_offset': 406}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 512, 'start_offset': 498}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "Kathy Castor to Heidi \n  VanGenderen....................................................    78\n\n \n  COLORADO'S ROADMAP FOR CLEAN ENERGY ACTION: LESSONS FROM STATE AND \n                             LOCAL LEADERS\n\n                              ----------                             \n\n\n                        THURSDAY, AUGUST 1, 2019\n\n                          House of Representatives,\n                    Select Committee on the Climate Crisis,\n                                                    Washington, DC."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 54, 'start_offset': 45}}, 'display_name': 'TIME'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 90, 'start_offset': 60}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 96, 'start_offset': 92}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 115, 'start_offset': 97}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 121, 'start_offset': 117}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 126, 'start_offset': 123}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 139, 'start_offset': 136}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 143, 'start_offset': 140}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 164, 'start_offset': 145}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 173, 'start_offset': 166}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 182, 'start_offset': 179}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    The committee met, pursuant to call, at 9:10 a.m., at \nUniversity of Colorado-Boulder, 2450 Kittredge Loop Dr., Wolf \nLaw Building 401 UCB, Wittemyer Courtroom, Boulder, CO, Hon.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 13, 'start_offset': 1}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\nKathy Castor presiding.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 36, 'start_offset': 14}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 52, 'start_offset': 46}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Present: Representatives Castor, Casten, Neguse, and \nGraves.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 41, 'start_offset': 19}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Also present: Representative DeGette.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 22, 'start_offset': 16}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Chairwoman Castor.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 40, 'start_offset': 22}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 82, 'start_offset': 77}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Welcome, everyone, to the House Select \nCommittee on the Climate Crisis, our first national field \nhearing.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'The committee will come to order.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 33, 'start_offset': 28}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Without objection, the Chair is authorized to declare a \nrecess of the committee at any time.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 36, 'start_offset': 10}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 47, 'start_offset': 40}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    I am Congresswoman Kathy Castor of Florida.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 55, 'start_offset': 47}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'I am honored to \nbe here in the great State of Colorado.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 52, 'start_offset': 24}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 84, 'start_offset': 76}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Without objection, Representative Diana DeGette, the \ngentlewoman from Colorado, shall be permitted to join the \ncommittee on the dais and be recognized for questioning of \nwitnesses.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 10, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 35, 'start_offset': 27}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 185, 'start_offset': 163}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 191, 'start_offset': 186}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n    Today we will discuss Colorado's state and local efforts to \nreduce greenhouse gas emissions and expand the deployment of \nclean energy and clean vehicles at the Select Committee's first \nfield hearing."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 35, 'start_offset': 26}}, 'display_name': 'TIME'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'So I recognize myself for 5 minutes to give an \nopening statement.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 39, 'start_offset': 34}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 66, 'start_offset': 61}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n    Thank you all for joining us today for the committee's \nfirst field hearing."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 50, 'start_offset': 42}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'I am excited to be in the great State of \nColorado as the committee works to develop a national climate \nplan.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'We need to build on what is working in states and \ncommunities across this great country.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 55, 'start_offset': 43}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    It is appropriate that we are here on Colorado Day.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 16, 'start_offset': 11}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 40, 'start_offset': 32}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'It is \nthe 143rd anniversary of Colorado becoming a state.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    [Applause.]'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 22, 'start_offset': 16}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Chairwoman Castor.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 63, 'start_offset': 55}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "Natural resources have always been a \ncritical part of Colorado's economy."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 5, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 22, 'start_offset': 10}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Today, in this century of \nthe climate crisis, those resources also include the \nintellectual and entrepreneurial resources.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 54, 'start_offset': 31}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 82, 'start_offset': 58}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 98, 'start_offset': 94}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 104, 'start_offset': 100}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 158, 'start_offset': 148}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'We have seen some \nof these in the past couple of days at the National Renewable \nEnergy Lab, NCAR, NOAA, and with scientists and students here \nat UC-Boulder.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'They are doing the cutting-edge research on the \nclimate crisis and the solutions to tackle the crisis.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 61, 'start_offset': 37}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 123, 'start_offset': 118}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 137, 'start_offset': 125}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'We are \nalso honored that our recent House of Representatives \ncolleague, now Governor Polis, is spending part of his first \nColorado Day as governor with us.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    When we say the states are the laboratories of democracy, \nwe mean that literally here.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 8, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Colorado is home to some of the \nleading research in climate change and clean energy.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 7, 'start_offset': 4}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'And one of \nthe most important things we can do as policymakers is make \nsure that clean technology can move from the lab to the market.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 88, 'start_offset': 81}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\nThat is what creates jobs, that is what cuts pollution, and \nthat is what makes America the leader in clean energy.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'We need \nto build the clean energy economy to solve the climate crisis.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 13, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Colorado in particular has been a leader in the clean \nenergy revolution.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 11, 'start_offset': 7}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 63, 'start_offset': 55}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 98, 'start_offset': 90}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "In the 2019 legislative session, the \nGovernor and the Colorado legislature have added to Colorado's \nclean energy legacy by enacting several bills focused on \ndeploying more energy efficiency, renewable energy, and \nelectric vehicles."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Equally important, they also created new \nprograms to support the energy workforce, the clean energy \nworkforce.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 5, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 136, 'start_offset': 113}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "Today we will be learning more about those policies \nand their benefits from a variety of perspectives to inform the \nSelect Committee's work."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    The climate crisis is the challenge of our lifetime.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'When \nwe confront it, it makes us realize that we are all in this \ntogether and that it will take creativity, innovation, and \npersistence by everyone to solve it.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 45, 'start_offset': 38}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 60, 'start_offset': 55}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Those same qualities are \nwhat helped America land the first person on the moon.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 33, 'start_offset': 29}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\nRecently, we celebrated the 50th anniversary of the Apollo 11 \nmission.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 11, 'start_offset': 6}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 49, 'start_offset': 42}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Those first steps on the moon proved that America can \ndo anything when we work together.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 62, 'start_offset': 56}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 88, 'start_offset': 81}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 115, 'start_offset': 110}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 132, 'start_offset': 124}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 181, 'start_offset': 164}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 215, 'start_offset': 192}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "I have always found an extra \nmeasure of inspiration in Apollo because I am from Florida, and \nbecause when I first came to Congress I had the honor of \ninheriting John F. Kennedy's office in the Cannon House Office \nBuilding."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 45, 'start_offset': 42}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 64, 'start_offset': 59}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n    A lot of people don't know this, but JFK was also the first \npresident to receive a warning about how humans were changing \nour climate."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Every president since then has received starker \nand starker warnings from the scientific community about the \nconsequences of carbon pollution and climate change.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 64, 'start_offset': 59}}, 'display_name': 'LOC'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Landing a man on the moon and returning him safely to Earth \nwas a grand challenge.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 12, 'start_offset': 7}}, 'display_name': 'LOC'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "Making Earth's atmosphere safe for \neveryone is now a grander one for all of us."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n    We don't have time to waste."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'We need to act as swiftly as \npossible.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Our next moonshot is solving the climate crisis.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'I \nknow we can do it.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 19, 'start_offset': 11}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'And I know Colorado is going to help us lead \nthe way.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 33, 'start_offset': 27}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 184, 'start_offset': 172}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 190, 'start_offset': 186}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 211, 'start_offset': 193}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 238, 'start_offset': 211}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 272, 'start_offset': 264}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 315, 'start_offset': 275}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 326, 'start_offset': 321}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 405, 'start_offset': 361}}, 'display_name': 'WORK_OF_ART'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 419, 'start_offset': 405}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 480, 'start_offset': 475}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n    [The statement of Ms. Castor follows:]\n                               __________\n\n              Opening Statement (As Prepared for Delivery)\n\n                    Rep. Kathy Castor (D-FL), Chair\n\n           U.S. House Select Committee on the Climate Crisis\n\n  Colorado's Roadmap for Clean Energy Action: Lessons from State and \n                             Local Leaders\n\n                             August 1, 2019\n\n    Good morning and thank you for joining us for our first field \nhearing."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 48, 'start_offset': 40}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "I'm excited to be in the great State of Colorado because as \nthis committee works on a national climate plan, we need to build on \nwhat's working in our states."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 32, 'start_offset': 20}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 43, 'start_offset': 38}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 67, 'start_offset': 59}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    We are here on Colorado Day--the 143rd anniversary of Colorado \nbecoming a state.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 63, 'start_offset': 55}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "Natural resources have always been a critical part of \nColorado's economy."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 19, 'start_offset': 3}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 122, 'start_offset': 104}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'In the 21st century, those also include the \nintellectual and entrepreneurial resources we have seen in the past few \ndays visiting national and state scientists, who are doing cutting edge \nresearch on the climate crisis and solutions for it.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 61, 'start_offset': 37}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 123, 'start_offset': 118}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'We are also \nhonored that our recent House of Representatives colleague, now \nGovernor Polis, is spending part of his first Colorado Day as governor \nwith us.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    When we say the states are laboratories of democracy, we mean that \nliterally here.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 8, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Colorado is home to some of the leading research in \nclimate change and clean energy.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 7, 'start_offset': 4}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 212, 'start_offset': 205}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "And one of the most important things \nwe can do as policymakers is make sure clean technology can move from \nthe lab to the market--that's what creates jobs, that's what cuts \npollution, that's what makes America a leader in the clean energy \neconomy we have to build to solve the climate crisis."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 13, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Colorado in particular has been a leader in the clean energy \nrevolution.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 11, 'start_offset': 7}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 58, 'start_offset': 50}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 94, 'start_offset': 86}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "In the 2019 legislative session, the governor and Colorado \nlegislature have added to Colorado's clean energy legacy by enacting \nseveral bills focused on deploying more energy efficiency, renewable \nenergy and electric vehicles."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Equally important, they also created new \nprograms to support the energy workforce.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 5, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 136, 'start_offset': 114}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "Today we will be learning \nmore about those policies and their benefits from a variety of \nperspectives to inform the Select Committee's work."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    The climate crisis is a huge problem.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': "When we confront it, it makes \nus realize that we're all in this together."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'And that it will take \ncreativity, innovation and persistence by everyone to solve it.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 49, 'start_offset': 42}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 64, 'start_offset': 59}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Those same qualities are what helped America land the first men on \nthe moon.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 32, 'start_offset': 28}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Recently, we celebrated the 50th anniversary of the Apollo 11 \nmission.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 11, 'start_offset': 6}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 49, 'start_offset': 42}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Those first steps on the moon proved that America can do \nanything when we work together.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 60, 'start_offset': 54}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 85, 'start_offset': 78}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 112, 'start_offset': 107}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 129, 'start_offset': 121}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 177, 'start_offset': 160}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "I've always found an extra measure of \ninspiration in Apollo because I'm from Florida, and because when I \nfirst came to Congress, I had to honor of inheriting John F. Kennedy's \nformer office."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 45, 'start_offset': 42}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 64, 'start_offset': 59}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n    A lot of people don't know this, but JFK was also the first \npresident to receive a warning about how humans were changing our \nclimate."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Every president since then has received starker and starker \nwarnings from the scientific community about the consequences of carbon \npollution and climate change.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 64, 'start_offset': 59}}, 'display_name': 'LOC'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Landing a man on the moon and returning him safely to Earth was a \ngrand challenge.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 12, 'start_offset': 7}}, 'display_name': 'LOC'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "Making Earth's atmosphere safe for everyone is an even \ngrander one."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 15, 'start_offset': 9}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    The Apollo program was a national effort that mobilized our \nscientific and engineering capabilities in the federal government, \nacademic institutions and private industry.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'The climate crisis requires \nthat same commitment and more.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 21, 'start_offset': 16}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'As we will hear today the solutions have \nalready started with our state and local governments.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'We need to act as \nswiftly as possible to follow your lead.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Our next moonshot is solving the climate crisis.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'I know we can do \nit.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 19, 'start_offset': 11}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'And I know Colorado is going to help us lead the way.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 159, 'start_offset': 149}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n\n    Now I am going to yield the balance of my time to another \ninspiration for all of us, the great representative of this \ncommunity, Congressman Joe Neguse.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 17, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'TIME'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 22, 'start_offset': 19}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Good morning, Joe.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    [Applause.]'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 15, 'start_offset': 9}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Mr. Neguse.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 13, 'start_offset': 8}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 85, 'start_offset': 78}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 121, 'start_offset': 116}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 159, 'start_offset': 139}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Well, I first want to say thank you to Madam \nChairwoman Castor for selecting Boulder as the location for the \nvery first field hearing of the Select Committee on the Climate \nCrisis.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 22, 'start_offset': 15}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'And welcome to Boulder to my colleagues.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 154, 'start_offset': 141}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'It is such an \nhonor to be able to join the committee in visiting my home \nstate, my home district, my home town, and my alma mater, CU \nand CU Law School.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 43, 'start_offset': 38}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    So I want to thank everyone here today, the witnesses who \nwill be testifying, the many activists and local leaders who \nhave helped in so many different ways in the fight against the \nexistential threat of climate change.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 90, 'start_offset': 69}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 124, 'start_offset': 116}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 167, 'start_offset': 146}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 183, 'start_offset': 174}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 212, 'start_offset': 185}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 225, 'start_offset': 218}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 269, 'start_offset': 259}}, 'display_name': 'TIME'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 374, 'start_offset': 352}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    I in particular want to recognize my fellow committee \nmembers, Representative Casten from the great State of \nIllinois; the Ranking Member, Representative Graves from \nLouisiana; Representative Buddy Carter from Georgia, who \nunfortunately had to leave last night but joined us for much of \nthe trip; and, of course, the dean of our delegation, \nRepresentative DeGette.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 67, 'start_offset': 60}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Thank you all for being willing to \nspend your time here in Boulder.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 48, 'start_offset': 41}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 58, 'start_offset': 50}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 73, 'start_offset': 65}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 103, 'start_offset': 98}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 164, 'start_offset': 121}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    I can think of no better place than Boulder, Colorado, and \nColorado as a state, to host the first field hearing of the \nSelect Committee on the Climate Crisis.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 61, 'start_offset': 44}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'It is the epicenter of \nclimate research in the United States.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 107, 'start_offset': 90}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 115, 'start_offset': 111}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 127, 'start_offset': 123}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 139, 'start_offset': 135}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 148, 'start_offset': 144}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'It has been an honor to \nbe able to visit with a number of scientists over the course of \nthe last two days at NREL and at NOAA and at UCAR and NCAR and \nCIRES and so many other of the wonderful Federal research \nlaboratories that we have here in our state that we are so \nlucky and blessed to be able to call home.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 31, 'start_offset': 26}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n    So I look forward to today's proceedings."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 190, 'start_offset': 180}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "This climate \nemergency requires us to take comprehensive and bold action, in \nmy view, and, I believe, in the view of the members of this \ncommittee, and I am so grateful for the Chairwoman's leadership \non that front."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    With that, I would yield back.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 22, 'start_offset': 16}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Chairwoman Castor.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 29, 'start_offset': 11}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Thank you, Congressman Neguse.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 83, 'start_offset': 74}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    At this time, I will recognize our Ranking Member, Garret \nGraves of Louisiana, for an opening statement.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 15, 'start_offset': 9}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Mr. Graves.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Thank you, Madam Chair.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    I want to thank all of you for being here to participate in \nyour government.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 30, 'start_offset': 13}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'This is what the United States looks like, and \nI really do appreciate every single one of you being here to \nshare your thoughts, to participate, and to ensure that you are \nbeing represented.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Governor, I want to thank you for being here.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 67, 'start_offset': 30}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'I had the \nchance to serve on the House Natural Resources Committee with \nyour governor, certainly a very well-equipped, bright guy.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'And \nI have to tell you, I miss you, I miss working with you on the \ncommittee.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'We had a number of amendments that we were able to \nwork on together.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'But congratulations to you, and I have no \ndoubt that you are going to do great things here, so thank you \nfor being with us.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Congressman Neguse, I want to thank you as well.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 41, 'start_offset': 32}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 49, 'start_offset': 42}}, 'display_name': 'TIME'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'The short \ntrip--I arrived just yesterday morning.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'This place has been \namazing, it really has.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'The people have been amazing.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Mayor, I want to thank you very much for being here and for \nwelcoming us as well.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Climate change.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 27, 'start_offset': 18}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'I represent south Louisiana.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'We have to get \nthis right, but we have to get this right.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'I want to explain \nwhat I mean there.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 10, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 36, 'start_offset': 29}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 46, 'start_offset': 38}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    First of all, we are in Boulder, Colorado.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'So we can sit \nhere and we can talk about the symptoms of climate change and \nwhat is going to happen here and what has happened here.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Let me \ntell you about where I live.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 36, 'start_offset': 18}}, 'display_name': 'QUANTITY'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 56, 'start_offset': 51}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    We have lost 2,000 square miles of our state, 2,000.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'How \nbig is that?'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 36, 'start_offset': 11}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 55, 'start_offset': 53}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 68, 'start_offset': 63}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'If it were the State of Rhode Island, we would \nhave 49 states today, alright?'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': "This isn't some place where \nbirds and fish live."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'This is people.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'This is homes.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'This is \nbusinesses.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'This is history.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 37, 'start_offset': 28}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 86, 'start_offset': 65}}, 'display_name': 'LOC'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Our tourism department years ago--we have this area called \nthe Atchafalaya Basin.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'It is one of the only open river \nfloodplains undisturbed in the nation, and it is just teeming \nwith wildlife.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'It is amazing.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Bears and alligators and deer, \njust a really amazing place.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 79, 'start_offset': 58}}, 'display_name': 'LOC'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 88, 'start_offset': 81}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "But they kicked off this tourism \ncampaign, and they said the Atchafalaya Basin, America's \nforeign country."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'And I was like, oh, that is awesome.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'And it \nis, it is awesome.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    But you know what?'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 23, 'start_offset': 14}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'That is south Louisiana, the place, the \npeople that I represent, the culture, the music, the food, the \npeople.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'There is nowhere else.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 99, 'start_offset': 74}}, 'display_name': 'TIME'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 128, 'start_offset': 118}}, 'display_name': 'TIME'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'And to watch that disappear, \nliterally--we lose a football field of land approximately every \nhour, a football field every hour.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    So sea rise is one of the contributing factors.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'There are a \nfew others.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'It is one of the contributing factors for our loss.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 74, 'start_offset': 32}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 84, 'start_offset': 80}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\nYou can look and you have seen the International Panel on \nClimate Change, the IPCC.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'You looked at their projections of \nsea rise.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 27, 'start_offset': 18}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "We don't have the Flatirons."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 32, 'start_offset': 23}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'If we have a slope in \nLouisiana, it goes from here to there.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'So when sea rises, it \ninundates.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'It inundates our homes, it inundates our businesses, \nit inundates our history, it inundates our ecosystem.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 78, 'start_offset': 75}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 115, 'start_offset': 111}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 143, 'start_offset': 137}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Actually, I worked on an amendment in one of our \ncommittees--I think Joe was about to throw something at me--\nwhere I tried to get Cajuns deemed an endangered species.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n[Laughter.]'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n    It didn't work."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    So from home, from the people I represent, we have to get \nthis right.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Now, let me explain the other reason we have to get this \nright.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 158, 'start_offset': 141}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 164, 'start_offset': 159}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'We have had people, experts, come before our committee \nwho have said we can cut every bit of emissions, every single \nbit of emissions from the United States today, everything, and \nit is not going to change the trajectory of warming.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 24, 'start_offset': 17}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    This place, Boulder, is amazing.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 9, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 75, 'start_offset': 42}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Yesterday I had the \nopportunity to go to the National Renewable Energy Lab.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'I have been to CIRES before.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 52, 'start_offset': 16}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'I have been \nto the Earth System Research Laboratory before.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 204, 'start_offset': 199}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'This place is \ngoing to be absolutely key in solving the problem, and what I \nmean by that is the experts, the facilities, the scientists \nthat you have here, the innovation, the moon shot that the \nChair just talked about.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    But when you look at what some places have done, up in the \nnortheast, some of the efforts to go very, very aggressive, \nthey have actually caused energy prices to triple those \ncompared to my home state.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': "In my home state, we can't afford \nit."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'We have a high rate of poverty.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': "We can't afford a tripling \nof energy."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 102, 'start_offset': 96}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'They have actually carried out policies that have \nrequired the importation of natural gas from Russia.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'They have \ncaused folks to burn wood in stoves in their homes.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'They have \ncaused the burning of heating oil.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 18, 'start_offset': 8}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 80, 'start_offset': 68}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    In California, we have increased our dependence upon oil \nfrom Saudi Arabia.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 83, 'start_offset': 71}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Let me say that again: We have increased our \ndependence upon oil from Saudi Arabia.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Here is a little-known fact.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 20, 'start_offset': 3}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 26, 'start_offset': 21}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 78, 'start_offset': 76}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 117, 'start_offset': 100}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 128, 'start_offset': 122}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'In the United States today we \nhave reduced emissions greater than the next 12 countries \ncombined, the United States has twelve countries combined.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 194, 'start_offset': 187}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 216, 'start_offset': 208}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 247, 'start_offset': 230}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 293, 'start_offset': 276}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 392, 'start_offset': 378}}, 'display_name': 'QUANTITY'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 399, 'start_offset': 394}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 464, 'start_offset': 450}}, 'display_name': 'QUANTITY'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 541, 'start_offset': 535}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'So \nwe can continue down this path of making this an incredibly \npolarizing issue and make it this big partisan fight, or we can \nrecognize that we are all in this together, not just in \nBoulder, not just in Colorado, not just in the United States, \nbut the globe, because as the United States has been the world \nleader in reduced carbon emissions greenhouse gas emissions by \na billion tons, China during that same period of time has \nincreased by 4 billion tons, more than offsetting every bit of \nprogress we have made here in the States.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Let me say it again.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 19, 'start_offset': 12}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 29, 'start_offset': 21}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 155, 'start_offset': 148}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 179, 'start_offset': 171}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 211, 'start_offset': 194}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'This place, Boulder, Colorado, the \nscientists, the experts, the facilities you have here, this \nplace is going to lead the innovation not just for Boulder, not \njust for Colorado, not just for the United States, but for the \nworld.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'And we are going to have to keep working together and \nstop this ridiculousness about all the partisan fighting that \nwe are seeing on this issue and virtually everything else, \nbecause we are all in this together.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 44, 'start_offset': 34}}, 'display_name': 'NORP'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 54, 'start_offset': 46}}, 'display_name': 'NORP'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n    It doesn't matter if you are Republican, Democrat, green, \npurple, blue, white, whatever."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': "When your land is being taken, \nwhen your home is going underwater, when your business is going \nunderwater, when your history, your culture is going \nunderwater, it doesn't matter."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': "It doesn't matter what label."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'It \naffects every single one of us.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    So let me say it again, Madam Chairwoman.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 41, 'start_offset': 34}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 51, 'start_offset': 43}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'I want to thank \nyou for choosing Boulder, Colorado.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 3, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 26, 'start_offset': 19}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 81, 'start_offset': 71}}, 'display_name': 'TIME'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Joe, Congresswoman DeGette, \nI want to thank you very much for hosting this today.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\nCongressman Casten, thanks for coming.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'And most importantly, I \nwant to thank you all for being here to participate in your \ngovernment, and we have got to work together to figure out a \nsolution that gets it right and gets it right.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    I yield back.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    [Applause.]'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 22, 'start_offset': 16}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Chairwoman Castor.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Thank you.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 21, 'start_offset': 15}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Thank you, Mr. Graves.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Now we will move on to our witnesses.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 16, 'start_offset': 13}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 29, 'start_offset': 24}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    We have two panels today.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 9, 'start_offset': 4}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 45, 'start_offset': 34}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 80, 'start_offset': 62}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'The first panel is the Honorable \nJared Polis, and I yield to Congressman Neguse to introduce the \nGovernor.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 15, 'start_offset': 9}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Mr. Neguse.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Thank you, Madam Chair.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 16, 'start_offset': 11}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 55, 'start_offset': 47}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 68, 'start_offset': 57}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'I am proud today to \nintroduce the Governor of Colorado, Jared Polis.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 47, 'start_offset': 36}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 125, 'start_offset': 78}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Before being elected governor, Jared Polis served as a \nboard member and Chair of the Colorado State Board of \nEducation.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 41, 'start_offset': 33}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 47, 'start_offset': 44}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 71, 'start_offset': 49}}, 'display_name': 'LOC'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 106, 'start_offset': 101}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "He was then elected to represent Colorado's 2nd \nCongressional District, which I am honored to serve today."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 12, 'start_offset': 9}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 51, 'start_offset': 37}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 126, 'start_offset': 118}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 156, 'start_offset': 149}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 169, 'start_offset': 165}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n    The 2nd District stretches from Larimer County and the \nWyoming border to the central mountains at the heart of \nColorado's tourism economy, to Boulder and the U.S. 36 high-\ntech corridor."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 37, 'start_offset': 20}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 87, 'start_offset': 82}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    In his time in the United States House of Representatives, \nthen-Congressman Polis was a strong advocate for finding \nsolutions to environmental issues.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'He was a national leader for \nprotecting our treasured public lands and addressing climate \nchange.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 19, 'start_offset': 11}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 61, 'start_offset': 44}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 87, 'start_offset': 63}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 132, 'start_offset': 122}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 141, 'start_offset': 137}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 170, 'start_offset': 162}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 246, 'start_offset': 243}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 280, 'start_offset': 276}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    After 10 years of honorable service in the United States \nHouse of Representatives, he successfully ran for governor last \nyear, in 2018, on the platform of full-day kindergarten for \nall, reducing health care costs, and transitioning to 100 \npercent renewable energy by 2040.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 32, 'start_offset': 24}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 45, 'start_offset': 34}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 113, 'start_offset': 108}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 127, 'start_offset': 114}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    As the Governor of Colorado, Jared Polis has made \nsignificant progress towards these goals during his first seven \nmonths in office, and he has left incredibly large shoes for me \nto fill as the congressman for this congressional district.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 59, 'start_offset': 37}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 66, 'start_offset': 61}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n    I am thrilled to welcome him to the Select Committee's \nfirst field hearing to share his testimony and his experience."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 40, 'start_offset': 32}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 53, 'start_offset': 42}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\nPlease welcome our Governor of Colorado, Jared Polis.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    [Applause.]'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 22, 'start_offset': 16}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Chairwoman Castor.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 45, 'start_offset': 39}}, 'display_name': 'TIME'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "And without objection, the witness' 5-\nminute testimony will be entered into the record."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 67, 'start_offset': 61}}, 'display_name': 'TIME'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    At this time, Governor, you are recognized to give a 5-\nminute presentation.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 130, 'start_offset': 125}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n\n  STATEMENT OF THE HONORABLE JARED POLIS, GOVERNOR OF COLORADO\n\n                    STATEMENT OF JARED POLIS\n\n    Governor Polis.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 12, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'TIME'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 72, 'start_offset': 51}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 95, 'start_offset': 74}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 120, 'start_offset': 98}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Good morning, Madam Chair, Ranking Member \nGraves, Representative Neguse, Representative Casten, \nRepresentative DeGette.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 69, 'start_offset': 52}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'I had the pleasure of serving with many \nof you for a number of years.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 9, 'start_offset': 4}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 22, 'start_offset': 14}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 30, 'start_offset': 25}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 122, 'start_offset': 114}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "And today, on Colorado's 143rd \nbirthday, which Madam Chair so kindly recognized, I am honored \nto welcome you to Colorado for a very important field hearing \nto discuss climate change, an existential threat to our \nsecurity, our health, our economy, our public lands and \necosystems, and our very way of life."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 13, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 72, 'start_offset': 54}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 124, 'start_offset': 103}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n    Colorado's climate has warmed substantially over the past \n30 years, and even more than that over the last half century."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 5, 'start_offset': 1}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\nTime is quickly running out to take bold action to reverse and \nalter the current trajectory.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 16, 'start_offset': 8}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n    In Colorado, we know this hotter, more erratic, drier \nfuture isn't some dystopian vision."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'It is impacting us right \nnow.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'It is impacting our dwindling water supply, impacting our \nfarming and ranching communities, our outdoor recreation \nindustry, our wildlife and ecological diversity.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'It is causing \nmore frequent, more devastating, and more expensive national \ndisasters, which also costs the Federal government money.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    If we want to preserve our way of life for future \ngenerations, we need to take bold action to address the climate \ncrisis.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    We have more than just a moral imperative to combat climate \nchange.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 11, 'start_offset': 3}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 59, 'start_offset': 52}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'In Colorado, as an example, and, of course, across \nAmerica, we also have an economic imperative to lead the global \ngreen energy revolution, to make the future work for us.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    We have a choice.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'We can be a leader in renewable energy, \nor we can let other countries develop the technologies, create \nthe jobs, and reap the rewards of the renewable energy future.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 16, 'start_offset': 8}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 63, 'start_offset': 40}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    In Colorado, as you have seen over the last couple of days, \nwe chose to lead.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 44, 'start_offset': 33}}, 'display_name': 'PERCENT'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 93, 'start_offset': 89}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'I ran on a platform of achieving 100 percent \nrenewable energy across our great state by 2040 because I know \nthat that will preserve our way of life and grow our economy \nwell into the future.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 52, 'start_offset': 50}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 147, 'start_offset': 136}}, 'display_name': 'PERCENT'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 199, 'start_offset': 195}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'This commitment was inspired and informed \nby the 14 towns and counties across our state that have also \nadopted the call of getting to 100 percent of their electricity \nfrom renewable energy by 2040, or in many cases even sooner.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 55, 'start_offset': 48}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 62, 'start_offset': 59}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    That is why my administration released our Roadmap to 100 \nPercent Renewable Energy and Bold Climate Action.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'You have a \ncopy of that in front of you as an exhibit.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 70, 'start_offset': 62}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "This Roadmap \noutlines how we will drive innovation and build Colorado's \neconomy by continuing and growing our leadership in green \nenergy development."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 68, 'start_offset': 46}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    We have taken significant strides during my first seven \nmonths in office to put us on the path to achieving this bold \ngoal.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'But the truth is that through price reductions and \ntechnological advances, the shift towards renewable energy is \nalready happening, and that is good news.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 35, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 56, 'start_offset': 53}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 99, 'start_offset': 82}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    The Bureau of Labor Statistics reports that the two fastest \ngrowing jobs in the United States right now are wind turbine \ntechnicians and solar panel installers.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 11, 'start_offset': 3}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 46, 'start_offset': 35}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 67, 'start_offset': 58}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 105, 'start_offset': 92}}, 'display_name': 'QUANTITY'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 122, 'start_offset': 114}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 175, 'start_offset': 150}}, 'display_name': 'QUANTITY'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'In Colorado, our \nlargest utility, Xcel Energy, announced last fall that they \nwould retire 660 megawatts of coal a decade early and replace \nit with more than 1,800 megawatts of wind, solar, and battery \nstorage.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 44, 'start_offset': 27}}, 'display_name': 'MONEY'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'In doing so, they estimate over $200 million in \nsavings for customers with no impact on reliability.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 40, 'start_offset': 36}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 93, 'start_offset': 83}}, 'display_name': 'PERCENT'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 101, 'start_offset': 97}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 125, 'start_offset': 114}}, 'display_name': 'PERCENT'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 158, 'start_offset': 154}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 256, 'start_offset': 239}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n    This effort is just a piece of Xcel's broader commitment to \nreduce emissions 80 percent by 2030 and produce 100 percent \ncarbon-free electricity by 2050, a commitment that our state \nlegislature, working with us, codified in statute this past \nspring."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 45, 'start_offset': 37}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 57, 'start_offset': 47}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 95, 'start_offset': 67}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 187, 'start_offset': 179}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 219, 'start_offset': 214}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 296, 'start_offset': 285}}, 'display_name': 'PERCENT'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 325, 'start_offset': 320}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Other electric providers across Colorado--Holy Cross \nEnergy, Platte River Power Authority, and a number of other \nrural electric cooperatives--have also followed suit, and \nColorado is proud to have the very first municipal utility in \nthe entire nation to have already achieved 100 percent \nrenewable energy, the Aspen municipal utility.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    It is undeniable that companies see a profitable future in \nrenewables, and given the dire stakes, it is our job as \npolicymakers to accelerate the transition towards a cleaner, \ngreener, more sustainable, and more affordable energy future.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n    Let's take transportation, the nation's largest source of \ngreenhouse gas emissions."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 74, 'start_offset': 70}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'My very first executive order set \ninto motion the establishment of a Zero Emission Vehicle \nCenter, an investment in electric charging infrastructure, to \nmake it easier for consumers to choose electric vehicles.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    We also, for the grid, unlocked financing solutions, \nincluding securitization, to help reduce the cost of retiring \ncoal-fired plants.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 21, 'start_offset': 15}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 62, 'start_offset': 57}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'We also passed Senate Bill 181 to put health \nand safety first and give local residents a say in what happens \nin their communities when it comes to oil and gas drilling \noperations, in addition to setting up a process to minimize \nfugitive emissions of methane and other pollutants from oil and \ngas activities.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n    We don't have to choose between creating good jobs and \nsaving our air, our water, and our way of life."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'We can and we \nmust do both by growing our renewable energy sector.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 83, 'start_offset': 75}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    When it comes to renewable energy and climate action, I \nbelieve that Colorado has a lot to show the rest of the nation, \nand I have no doubt that we can take bold action at the Federal \nlevel as well.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 27, 'start_offset': 22}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 56, 'start_offset': 49}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 110, 'start_offset': 104}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'I was glad to see the House pass H.R. 9 to keep \nAmerica in the Paris Climate Agreement, and I hope the Senate \nfollows suit.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 22, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    The United States does not back down from a challenge.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'We \nare a nation of leaders, of doers, of dreamers.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 10, 'start_offset': 3}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'In America, we \nget to choose our own destiny.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 37, 'start_offset': 32}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 205, 'start_offset': 166}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 225, 'start_offset': 217}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 298, 'start_offset': 290}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 341, 'start_offset': 301}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 352, 'start_offset': 347}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 400, 'start_offset': 386}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 446, 'start_offset': 432}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 483, 'start_offset': 477}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 554, 'start_offset': 528}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n    [The statement of Governor Polis follows:]\n                              ----------                              \n\n\n               Written Testimony of Governor Jared Polis\n\n                          Governor of Colorado\n\n              House Select Committee on the Climate Crisis\n\n ``Colorado's Roadmap for Clean Energy Action: Lessons from State and \n                            Local Leaders''\n\n                             August 1, 2019\n\n    Good morning, Chairwoman Castor, Ranking Member Graves, and the \nmembers of the House Select Committee."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 67, 'start_offset': 62}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 131, 'start_offset': 126}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "Thank you for the opportunity to \ntestify in front of you all today here in the great State of Colorado \nfor your committee's first field hearing."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 27, 'start_offset': 16}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 51, 'start_offset': 47}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 86, 'start_offset': 78}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 166, 'start_offset': 153}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    My name is Jared Polis and I serve as the 43rd governor of the \nState of Colorado, and as such I welcome you to our great state for \nthis important Congressional field hearing.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 46, 'start_offset': 39}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 102, 'start_offset': 95}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 116, 'start_offset': 104}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 141, 'start_offset': 133}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 156, 'start_offset': 144}}, 'display_name': 'LOC'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 189, 'start_offset': 160}}, 'display_name': 'FAC'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 202, 'start_offset': 194}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "I was born and currently \nlive here in Boulder, and before serving as Governor, I represented \nBoulder, Fort Collins and the rest of Colorado's 2nd District in the \nHouse of Representatives for a decade."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 30, 'start_offset': 22}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 66, 'start_offset': 59}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 77, 'start_offset': 72}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 99, 'start_offset': 89}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "I am proud to see our Colorado \nRepresentatives Neguse and DeGette here today protecting Coloradans by \nleading our nation's efforts to combat the climate crisis on the Select \nCommittee."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 10, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 50, 'start_offset': 42}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 92, 'start_offset': 88}}, 'display_name': 'PERCENT'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n    Today, I will provide an overview of Colorado's urgent efforts to-\ndate to achieve 100% renewable energy and bold climate action."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 91, 'start_offset': 83}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'It is my \nhope that other states and the federal government can draw lessons from \nColorado to achieve substantial and permanent reductions in pollution \nand other activities that contribute to the climate crisis.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 70, 'start_offset': 66}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 80, 'start_offset': 72}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n                  coloradans leading on climate action\n    Since 2004, Colorado has been among the states leading the clean \nenergy transition.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Not only do we have a moral imperative to combat \nclimate change to protect the health of our communities and our \nenvironment, we also have an economic opportunity to lead the global \nclean energy revolution.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    We have a choice: we can be a leader in renewable energy, or we can \nlet other countries develop technologies, create the jobs, and reap the \nrewards of a renewable energy future.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 11, 'start_offset': 3}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'In Colorado, we have chosen to \nlead.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 39, 'start_offset': 35}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 51, 'start_offset': 41}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 74, 'start_offset': 72}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 103, 'start_offset': 98}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 174, 'start_offset': 171}}, 'display_name': 'PERCENT'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 182, 'start_offset': 178}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Renewable Energy Standard: In 2004, Coloradans approved Amendment \n37, which established the first voter-approved state renewable energy \nstandard, originally set at 10% by 2020 for our investor owned \nutilities.'}}
