{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 30, 'start_offset': 29}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 38, 'start_offset': 33}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 51, 'start_offset': 48}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 92, 'start_offset': 88}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 131, 'start_offset': 126}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 144, 'start_offset': 141}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 153, 'start_offset': 145}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 198, 'start_offset': 161}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 543, 'start_offset': 454}}, 'display_name': 'WORK_OF_ART'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 650, 'start_offset': 641}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 695, 'start_offset': 690}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 835, 'start_offset': 819}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "[\nError: Parse error on line 1:\n[House Hearing, 116 C\n-^\nExpecting 'STRING', 'NUMBER', 'NULL', 'TRUE', 'FALSE', '{', '[', ']'\nHouse Hearing, 116 Congress]\n[From the U.S. Government Publishing Office]\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n                      SOLVING THE CLIMATE CRISIS:\n                      OPPORTUNITIES IN AGRICULTURE\n\n=======================================================================\n\n                                HEARING\n\n                               BEFORE THE\n\n                        SELECT COMMITTEE ON THE\n                             CLIMATE CRISIS\n                        HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES\n\n                     ONE HUNDRED SIXTEENTH CONGRESS\n\n                             FIRST SESSION\n\n                               __________\n\n                              HEARING HELD\n                            OCTOBER 30, 2019\n\n                               __________\n\n                           Serial No."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 6, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 35, 'start_offset': 26}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 168, 'start_offset': 148}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 315, 'start_offset': 313}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 319, 'start_offset': 315}}, 'display_name': 'PRODUCT'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 350, 'start_offset': 340}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 357, 'start_offset': 353}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 519, 'start_offset': 508}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 529, 'start_offset': 520}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 583, 'start_offset': 576}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 590, 'start_offset': 585}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 604, 'start_offset': 591}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 616, 'start_offset': 606}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 652, 'start_offset': 643}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 670, 'start_offset': 662}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 678, 'start_offset': 672}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 722, 'start_offset': 708}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 734, 'start_offset': 724}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 770, 'start_offset': 762}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 796, 'start_offset': 786}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 828, 'start_offset': 821}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 857, 'start_offset': 849}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 887, 'start_offset': 880}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 910, 'start_offset': 900}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 952, 'start_offset': 939}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 974, 'start_offset': 966}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 1019, 'start_offset': 1007}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 1030, 'start_offset': 1020}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 1040, 'start_offset': 1032}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 1145, 'start_offset': 1140}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 1199, 'start_offset': 1189}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 1893, 'start_offset': 1885}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 1970, 'start_offset': 1967}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '116-13\n\n\n\n\n              [GRAPHIC(S) NOT AVAILABLE IN TIFF FORMAT]\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n                            www.govinfo.gov\n   Printed for the use of the Select Committee on the Climate Crisis\n                               __________\n\n                      U.S. GOVERNMENT PUBLISHING OFFICE\n                      \n39-635                     WASHINGTON : 2020 \n   \n   \n   \n   \n   \n   \n   \n   \n   \n   \n   \n   \n   \n   \n   \n   \n   \n   \n                 SELECT COMMITTEE ON THE CLIMATE CRISIS\n                     One Hundred Sixteenth Congress\n\n                      KATHY CASTOR, Florida, Chair\nBEN RAY LUJAN, New Mexico            GARRET GRAVES, Louisiana,\nSUZANNE BONAMICI, Oregon               Ranking Member\nJULIA BROWNLEY, California           MORGAN GRIFFITH, Virginia\nJARED HUFFMAN, California            GARY PALMER, Alabama\nA. DONALD McEACHIN, Virginia         BUDDY CARTER, Georgia\nMIKE LEVIN, California               CAROL MILLER, West Virginia\nSEAN CASTEN, Illinois                KELLY ARMSTRONG, North Dakota\nJOE NEGUSE, Colorado\n\n                              ----------                              \n\n                Ana Unruh Cohen, Majority Staff Director\n                  Marty Hall, Minority Staff Director\n                        climatecrisis.house.gov \n                        \n                        \n                        \n                        \n                        \n                        \n                        \n                        \n                        \n                        \n                        \n                        \n                        \n                        \n                        \n                        \n                        \n                        \n                            C O N T E N T S\n\n                              ----------                              \n\n                   STATEMENTS OF MEMBERS OF CONGRESS\n\n                                                                   Page\nHon.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 12, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 42, 'start_offset': 34}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 71, 'start_offset': 64}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 122, 'start_offset': 77}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 195, 'start_offset': 194}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 267, 'start_offset': 266}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 271, 'start_offset': 268}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Kathy Castor, a Representative in Congress from the State of \n  Florida, and Chair, Select Committee on the Climate Crisis:\n    Opening Statement............................................     1\n    Prepared Statement...........................................     3\nHon.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 14, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 44, 'start_offset': 36}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 75, 'start_offset': 66}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 95, 'start_offset': 81}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 113, 'start_offset': 97}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 211, 'start_offset': 210}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 276, 'start_offset': 255}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 283, 'start_offset': 278}}, 'display_name': 'WORK_OF_ART'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 340, 'start_offset': 317}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 412, 'start_offset': 411}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 484, 'start_offset': 483}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 495, 'start_offset': 485}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 525, 'start_offset': 497}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 535, 'start_offset': 527}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 582, 'start_offset': 555}}, 'display_name': 'FAC'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 635, 'start_offset': 633}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 707, 'start_offset': 705}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 718, 'start_offset': 708}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 722, 'start_offset': 720}}, 'display_name': 'NORP'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Garrett Graves, a Representative in Congress from the State \n  of Louisiana, and Ranking Member, Select Committee on the \n  Climate Crisis:\n    Opening Statement............................................     4\n\n                               WITNESSES\n\nJennifer Moore-Kucera, Ph.D., Climate Initiative Director, \n  American Farmland Trust\n    Oral Statement...............................................     5\n    Prepared Statement...........................................     7\nFred Yoder, Corn, Soybean & Wheat Farmer; Co-Chair, Solutions \n  from the Land\n    Oral Statement...............................................    16\n    Prepared Statement...........................................    17\nTina Owens, Sr.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 45, 'start_offset': 10}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 62, 'start_offset': 50}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 142, 'start_offset': 140}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 214, 'start_offset': 212}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 225, 'start_offset': 215}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 279, 'start_offset': 246}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 304, 'start_offset': 284}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 376, 'start_offset': 374}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 448, 'start_offset': 446}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 534, 'start_offset': 513}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 577, 'start_offset': 571}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 636, 'start_offset': 634}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 671, 'start_offset': 645}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 712, 'start_offset': 702}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 723, 'start_offset': 718}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 763, 'start_offset': 757}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 771, 'start_offset': 769}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 784, 'start_offset': 780}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 790, 'start_offset': 786}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 811, 'start_offset': 792}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 829, 'start_offset': 813}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Director, Agriculture Funding & Communication, \n  Danone North America\n    Oral Statement...............................................    21\n    Prepared Statement...........................................    23\nViral Amin, Vice President for Commercial Development & Strategy, \n  DTE Energy Resources\n    Oral Statement...............................................    26\n    Prepared Statement...........................................    28\n\n                       SUBMISSIONS FOR THE RECORD\n\nLetter from Defenders of Wildlife, submitted for the record by \n  Ms. Castor.....................................................    50\nReport, Climate Mitigation through Agricultural Productivity, \n  Innovation, and Trade, submitted for the record by Ms. Castor..    52\nReport, IPCC, 2014: Climate Change 2014: Synthesis Report.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 33, 'start_offset': 19}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 39, 'start_offset': 37}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 47, 'start_offset': 44}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 60, 'start_offset': 55}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 173, 'start_offset': 167}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 196, 'start_offset': 194}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 228, 'start_offset': 204}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 239, 'start_offset': 230}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 268, 'start_offset': 246}}, 'display_name': 'LOC'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 308, 'start_offset': 302}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 332, 'start_offset': 330}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 350, 'start_offset': 340}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 370, 'start_offset': 353}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 392, 'start_offset': 383}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 443, 'start_offset': 415}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 486, 'start_offset': 480}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 535, 'start_offset': 533}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 568, 'start_offset': 549}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 587, 'start_offset': 571}}, 'display_name': 'WORK_OF_ART'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 598, 'start_offset': 593}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 610, 'start_offset': 604}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 644, 'start_offset': 633}}, 'display_name': 'LOC'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 689, 'start_offset': 683}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 738, 'start_offset': 736}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n  Contribution of Working Groups I, II and III to the Fifth \n  Assessment Report of the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate \n  Change, submitted for the record by Mr. Graves.................    54\nChart, C02 Emissions Reductions, 2005-2017, from Global Carbon \n  Atlas, submitted for the record by Mr. Graves..................    54\nChart, California's Crude Oil Imports, by Source, 2014-2018, data \n  sourced from California Energy Commission, submitted for the \n  record by Mr. Graves...........................................    55\nArticle from Washington Examiner, ``Why Natural Gas from Putin's \n  Russia Has to Be Imported to New England,'' submitted for the \n  record by Mr. Graves...........................................    55\nLetter from Sens."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 14, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 31, 'start_offset': 16}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 46, 'start_offset': 33}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 64, 'start_offset': 55}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 83, 'start_offset': 78}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 126, 'start_offset': 120}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 185, 'start_offset': 183}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 262, 'start_offset': 259}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Maria Cantwell, Robert Menendez, Chuck Schumer, \n  and Ed Markey to President Trump, submitted for the record by \n  Mr. Graves.....................................................    55\n\n                                APPENDIX\n\nQuestions for the Record from Hon.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 12, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 40, 'start_offset': 16}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 97, 'start_offset': 95}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 131, 'start_offset': 128}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Kathy Castor to Jennifer \n  Moore-Kucera...................................................    55\nQuestions for the Record from Hon.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 12, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 26, 'start_offset': 16}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 36, 'start_offset': 34}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 70, 'start_offset': 67}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Kathy Castor to Tina Owens....    59\nQuestions for the Record from Hon.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 27, 'start_offset': 17}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 36, 'start_offset': 34}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 70, 'start_offset': 67}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Garret Graves to Tina Owens...    59\nQuestions for the Record from Hon.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 27, 'start_offset': 17}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 36, 'start_offset': 34}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 70, 'start_offset': 67}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Garret Graves to Fred Yoder...    63\nQuestions for the Record from Hon.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 210, 'start_offset': 201}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 228, 'start_offset': 212}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 280, 'start_offset': 251}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 318, 'start_offset': 302}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 403, 'start_offset': 393}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 409, 'start_offset': 405}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 463, 'start_offset': 454}}, 'display_name': 'TIME'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 477, 'start_offset': 474}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 507, 'start_offset': 479}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 512, 'start_offset': 509}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Garret Graves to Viral Amin...    64\n\n \n        SOLVING THE CLIMATE CRISIS: OPPORTUNITIES IN AGRICULTURE\n\n                              ----------                              \n\n\n                      WEDNESDAY, OCTOBER 30, 2019\n\n                     U.S. House of Representatives,\n                    Select Committee on the Climate Crisis,\n                                                   Washington, D.C.\n    The committee met, pursuant to call, at 2:35 p.m., in Room \n210, Cannon House Office Building, Hon.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 12, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Kathy Castor \n[chairwoman of the committee] presiding.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 36, 'start_offset': 14}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 46, 'start_offset': 38}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 56, 'start_offset': 48}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 108, 'start_offset': 59}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 120, 'start_offset': 114}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Present: Representatives Castor, Bonamici, Brownley, \nHuffman, Casten, Graves, Griffith, Palmer, Carter, and Miller.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 41, 'start_offset': 34}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 56, 'start_offset': 50}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Also Present: Representative Pingree\n    Ms. Castor.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'The committee will come to order.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Without \nobjection, the chair is authorized to declare a recess of the \ncommittee at any time.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 54, 'start_offset': 39}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 83, 'start_offset': 78}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Without objection, Representative Chellie Pingree, the \ngentlewoman from Maine, shall be permitted to join the \ncommittee on the dais and be recognized for questioning of \nwitnesses.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Welcome, everyone.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 5, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 34, 'start_offset': 26}}, 'display_name': 'NORP'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Today we will explore how American farms \ncan be part of climate solutions and examine climate smart \nagricultural practices that can reduce greenhouse gas emissions \nand, at the same time, increase soil health and carbon \nsequestration in agricultural lands, all while helping make \nfarms more resilient to the impacts of climate change.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 51, 'start_offset': 42}}, 'display_name': 'TIME'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'I would \nlike to recognize myself now for 5 minutes for an opening \nstatement.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 20, 'start_offset': 11}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 41, 'start_offset': 21}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Well, last week the Select Committee on the Climate Crisis \nbegan exploring natural climate solutions.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Nature gives us \neffective and inexpensive opportunities to keep our air and \nwater clean and to reduce carbon pollution.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 5, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Today, we will \ndiscuss similar opportunities in agriculture and how farmers \nare contributing to climate solutions and can do more.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 12, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Farmers are on the front lines of the climate crisis.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 18, 'start_offset': 1}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 31, 'start_offset': 24}}, 'display_name': 'LOC'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\nEarlier this year, the midwest experienced extreme rains \nfollowed by severe winds and blizzard conditions across the \nregion.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'The effects were devastating.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 63, 'start_offset': 57}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 82, 'start_offset': 74}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'The storms decimated \nlivestock, flooded some fields for months, and left millions of \nacres unable to be planted.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 35, 'start_offset': 17}}, 'display_name': 'LOC'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 73, 'start_offset': 59}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Some areas along the Missouri River \nare still flooded now 7 months later.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Similar stories can be told in other parts of our nation, \nwhether it is fires in the west or hurricanes in the southeast.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 55, 'start_offset': 42}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 103, 'start_offset': 64}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\nIn fact, extreme weather conditions made the past year one of \nthe worst agricultural years in decades.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 51, 'start_offset': 44}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "The climate crisis is \nincreasingly putting America's agriculture at risk through \nharsher floods, longer droughts, unexpected frosts, and other \nextreme weather events."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'You know, anyone who eats should care \nabout the climate crisis.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 14, 'start_offset': 8}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 31, 'start_offset': 21}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 55, 'start_offset': 48}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 109, 'start_offset': 99}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 240, 'start_offset': 214}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    In August, with Fred Yoder, I visited with Florida \nagriculture leaders that included citrus, strawberry, and dairy \nfarmers, timber, and ranching interests, along with \nagricultural extension scientists from the University of \nFlorida, and they advised me that rising temperatures and \nextreme events are impacting their operations and that they \nneed help adapting.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    And they impressed upon me that they also want to be part \nof the solution to the climate crisis, and they are not alone.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 26, 'start_offset': 19}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\nAs farmers across America increasingly wrestle with the impacts \nof higher temperatures, they are also looking for opportunities \nto help solve the climate crisis.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Through land management \nstrategies and smart partnerships, they can have an enormous \nimpact.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 7, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "America's farms are uniquely situated to become \npowerful carbon sinks, all while becoming more resilient to the \nimpacts of severe weather events."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 25, 'start_offset': 8}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 76, 'start_offset': 66}}, 'display_name': 'PERCENT'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 86, 'start_offset': 80}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    In the United States, agriculture is responsible for nearly \n10 percent of annual greenhouse gas emissions which primarily \ncome from nitrogen fertilizer applications and livestock.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 88, 'start_offset': 83}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'But \nthrough innovative and proven conservation practices that we \nwill hear about today, they can reduce these emissions.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    And farmers are already doing a lot to combat the climate \ncrisis, and we must invest in them to do even more.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 7, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "Climate \nsmart agricultural practices such as reducing tillage, planting \ncover crops, and diversifying crop rotations can increase \nfarmlands' potential to sequester carbon and mitigate climate \nchange."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'These practices often improve soil health and can also \nreduce costs, increase yields, and make farms more resilient to \nthe impacts of extreme weather.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    One of the most important things we can do to fight the \nclimate crisis is to protect our farmlands.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 28, 'start_offset': 21}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 60, 'start_offset': 43}}, 'display_name': 'QUANTITY'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'In the last several \ndecades, we have lost millions of acres of agricultural lands \nto development.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 226, 'start_offset': 217}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Protecting current farmland from development \nreduces the pressure to convert natural areas to new cropland, \nleaving intact the forests, the grasslands and wetlands to \nprovide the climate benefits that we discussed last week.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 13, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Congress has already taken some steps to incentivize \nclimate smart agricultural practices.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 32, 'start_offset': 28}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 87, 'start_offset': 50}}, 'display_name': 'LOC'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 136, 'start_offset': 92}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Congressionally \nauthorized USDA programs such as the Conservation Stewardship \nProgram and the Environmental Quality Incentives Program offer \nfarmers technical and financial assistance to increase \nconservation activities.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 37, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 180, 'start_offset': 134}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    The Conservation Reserve Program pays farmers to \nvoluntarily retire land from production for less resource-\nintensive uses, and the Agriculture Conservation Easement \nProgram permanently protects farmlands through agricultural \nconservation easements.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 13, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 55, 'start_offset': 51}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Congress passed important improvements in the 2018 Farm \nBill which increased and expanded upon these initiatives.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 9, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 59, 'start_offset': 27}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'The \nUSDA also administers the Rural Energy Savings Program and the \nRenewable Energy for America Program which helps support energy \nefficiency and renewable energy in rural communities.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'And, of \ncourse, the renewable fuel standards and federal tax incentives \nfor wind and solar have provided sustained economic benefits to \nfarmers in rural counties across the country, but there is more \nwork to do.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    We can help the agricultural sector increase their critical \nrole in carbon storage, and we can help farmers maintain and \nincrease their profitability while also helping to solve the \nclimate crisis.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 8, 'start_offset': 3}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'So today we have experts here who are going to \nhelp us develop those solutions and help us turn all of these \nthings into reality.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 53, 'start_offset': 47}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 80, 'start_offset': 72}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 162, 'start_offset': 156}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    At this time, I will recognize--since Mr. Graves is not \nhere, Mr. Griffith, if you would like to make any opening \ncomments, you are welcome, and Mr. Graves will still get his \nopportunity when he arrives.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 33, 'start_offset': 27}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 184, 'start_offset': 172}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 190, 'start_offset': 186}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 211, 'start_offset': 193}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 238, 'start_offset': 211}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 328, 'start_offset': 268}}, 'display_name': 'WORK_OF_ART'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 374, 'start_offset': 358}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 389, 'start_offset': 380}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n    [The statement of Ms. Castor follows:]\n                               __________\n\n              Opening Statement (As Prepared for Delivery)\n\n                    Rep. Kathy Castor (D-FL), Chair\n\n           U.S. House Select Committee on the Climate Crisis\n\n      ``Solving the Climate Crisis: Opportunities in Agriculture''\n\n                            October 30, 2019\n\n    Last week, our committee began exploring natural climate solutions."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\nNature gives us effective and inexpensive opportunities to keep our air \nand water clean and to reduce carbon pollution.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 5, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Today, we will discuss \nsimilar opportunities in agriculture and how farmers are contributing \nto climate solutions--and can do more.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 12, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Farmers are on the front lines of the climate crisis.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 18, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 31, 'start_offset': 24}}, 'display_name': 'LOC'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Earlier this \nyear, the Midwest experienced extreme rains followed by severe winds \nand blizzard conditions across the region.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 93, 'start_offset': 87}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 121, 'start_offset': 104}}, 'display_name': 'QUANTITY'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'The effects were \ndevastating: the storm decimated livestock, flooded some fields for \nmonths, and left millions of acres unable to be planted.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 36, 'start_offset': 18}}, 'display_name': 'LOC'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 78, 'start_offset': 60}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Some areas \nalong the Missouri River are still flooded now--seven months later.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 94, 'start_offset': 90}}, 'display_name': 'LOC'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 125, 'start_offset': 116}}, 'display_name': 'LOC'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n    Similar stories can be told in other parts of our nation, whether \nit's fires in the West or hurricanes in the Southeast."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 55, 'start_offset': 42}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 100, 'start_offset': 93}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'In fact, extreme \nweather conditions made the past year one of the worst for agriculture \nin decades.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 50, 'start_offset': 43}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "The climate crisis is increasingly putting America's \nagriculture at risk, through harsher floods, longer droughts, \nunexpected frosts, and other extreme weather events."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Anyone who eats \nshould care about the climate crisis.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 14, 'start_offset': 8}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 38, 'start_offset': 31}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 156, 'start_offset': 127}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    In August, I visited with Florida agriculture leaders that included \ncitrus, strawberries, dairy, timber and ranching and the University of \nFlorida ag extension scientists.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'The farmers and ranchers advised me \nthat rising temperatures and extreme events are impacting their \noperations and they need help adapting, and they impressed upon me that \nthey want to be part of the solution to the climate crisis.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    They are not alone.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 25, 'start_offset': 18}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "As farmers across America increasingly wrestle \nwith the impacts of higher temperatures, they're also looking for \nopportunities to help solve the climate crisis."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Through land management \nstrategies and smart partnerships, they can have an enormous impact.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 8, 'start_offset': 1}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\nAmerica's farms are uniquely situated to become powerful carbon sinks, \nall while becoming more resilient to the impacts of severe weather \nevents."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 25, 'start_offset': 8}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 76, 'start_offset': 58}}, 'display_name': 'PERCENT'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 86, 'start_offset': 80}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    In the United States, agriculture is responsible for nearly 10 \npercent of annual greenhouse gas emissions, which primarily come from \nnitrogen fertilizer application and livestock.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 85, 'start_offset': 80}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "But through innovative \nand proven conservation practices that we'll hear about today, they can \nreduce these emissions."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 12, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Farmers are already doing a lot to combat the climate crisis, and \nwe must invest in them to help them do even more.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': "Climate-smart \nagricultural practices, such as reducing tillage, planting cover crops, \nand diversifying crop rotations, can increase farmland's potential to \nsequester carbon and mitigate climate change."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'These practices to \nimprove soil health can also reduce costs, increase yields, and make \nfarms more resilient to the impacts of extreme weather.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    One of the most important things we can do to fight the climate \ncrisis is protect our farmlands.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 27, 'start_offset': 3}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 60, 'start_offset': 43}}, 'display_name': 'QUANTITY'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'In the last several decades, we have \nlost millions of acres of agricultural lands to development.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 218, 'start_offset': 209}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Protecting \ncurrent farmland from development reduces the pressure to convert \nnatural areas to new cropland, leaving intact the forests, grasslands, \nand wetlands to provide the climate benefits we discussed last week.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 13, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Congress has already taken steps to incentivize climate-smart \nagricultural practices.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 31, 'start_offset': 27}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 87, 'start_offset': 51}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Congressionally-authorized USDA programs--such \nas the Conservation Stewardship Program and the Environmental Quality \nIncentives Program--offer farmers technical and financial assistance to \nincrease conservation activities.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 32, 'start_offset': 4}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'The Conservation Reserve Program pays \nfarmers to voluntarily retire land from production for less resource-\nintensive uses.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 50, 'start_offset': 4}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'And the Agricultural Conservation Easement Program \npermanently protects farmland through agricultural conservation \neasements.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 8, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 55, 'start_offset': 51}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 66, 'start_offset': 56}}, 'display_name': 'WORK_OF_ART'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Congress also passed important improvements in the 2018 Farm \nBill, which increased and expanded upon these initiatives.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 13, 'start_offset': 9}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 63, 'start_offset': 31}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    The USDA also administers the Rural Energy Savings Program and the \nRenewable Energy for America Program which help support energy \nefficiency and renewable energy in rural communities.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'And, of course, \nthe Renewable Fuels Standard and federal tax incentives for wind and \nsolar have provided sustained economic benefits to farmers and rural \ncounties across the country.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    But there is still work to do.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    We can help the agricultural sector increase their critical role in \ncarbon storage.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'And we can help farmers maintain and increase their \nprofitability, while also helping solve the climate crisis.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 5, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 34, 'start_offset': 26}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "Today we'll \nexplore ways Congress can help make this a reality."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 18, 'start_offset': 10}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n\n    Mr. Griffith.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Well, I appreciate that, Madam Chair, but I \nanticipate that Ranking Member Graves will be here shortly.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 15, 'start_offset': 9}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Ms. Castor.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Okay.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': "Well, if the witnesses don't mind, when \nhe arrives, we may break in between witnesses and have him give \nsome opening statements, or he might want to just jump right \ninto the questions as well."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 62, 'start_offset': 57}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Now we will move on to our terrific panel before us today.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 54, 'start_offset': 51}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 61, 'start_offset': 58}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\nI will introduce each of you, and then we will go one by one \nwith testimony.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 39, 'start_offset': 18}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    First is Dr. Jennifer Moore-Kucera.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 66, 'start_offset': 43}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'She is the Climate \nInitiative Director at American Farmland Trust.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'She oversees \ntheir efforts to help states develop innovative policies and \nprograms that can maximize agriculture opportunities to combat \nthe climate crisis.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 20, 'start_offset': 17}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 40, 'start_offset': 36}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 81, 'start_offset': 44}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 96, 'start_offset': 85}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 157, 'start_offset': 153}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "Prior to joining AFT, she served in USDA's \nNatural Resource Conservation Service as west region soil \nhealth team leader and as the co-director for the USDA \nnorthwest climate hub."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 41, 'start_offset': 31}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 54, 'start_offset': 48}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Next, my good friend, Mr. Fred Yoder, is a fourth \ngeneration farmer.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 42, 'start_offset': 38}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "He grows corn, soybeans, and wheat in Ohio \non his family's farm and operates a retail seed business."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 50, 'start_offset': 28}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 170, 'start_offset': 153}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'He is \nalso the co-chair of Solutions for the Land and advocates for \nagriculture solutions to sustain productive, enhance climate \nresilience, and help the United States reach sustainable \ndevelopment goals.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 25, 'start_offset': 15}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 114, 'start_offset': 94}}, 'display_name': 'LOC'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Next, Ms. Tina Owens is the Senior Director of Agriculture \nFunding and Communication at Danone North America.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Her work \nfocuses on regenerative agriculture practices and financing.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 24, 'start_offset': 15}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\nShe has spent 2 decades leading sustainability and strategic \nsourcing in the food industry.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 25, 'start_offset': 15}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 87, 'start_offset': 51}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 111, 'start_offset': 91}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Next, Mr. Viral Amin is the Vice President of Commercial \nDevelopment and Strategy at DTE Energy Resources.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 10, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 165, 'start_offset': 156}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'DTE Energy is \na diversified energy company and develops renewable energy \nservices projects, including a dairy-based renewable gas \nprocessing facility in Wisconsin.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 44, 'start_offset': 32}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 117, 'start_offset': 108}}, 'display_name': 'TIME'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Before we turn to you, Dr. Moore-Kucera, we want to welcome \nthe ranking member, and if you would like 5 minutes to make \nopening remarks.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 15, 'start_offset': 9}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Mr. Graves.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Thank you for not late shaming me too much.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'I \napologize for being late, but thank you all for being here.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 80, 'start_offset': 75}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    I just very quickly want to say that I appreciate you all \nbeing here today.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Agriculture is a very important opportunity, \nvery important natural resource managers that have the \nopportunity, as I indicated, to be significant participants in \nour efforts to sequester greenhouse gases.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 115, 'start_offset': 99}}, 'display_name': 'PERCENT'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    If you look across the globe, approximately, I guess the \naverage for agriculture is emitting about 24 percent of the \ngreenhouse gases in different countries.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 20, 'start_offset': 3}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 44, 'start_offset': 29}}, 'display_name': 'PERCENT'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 128, 'start_offset': 111}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'In the United States, \nit is about 8 percent, indicating it is a more efficient \nagricultural practice here in the United States which does \nsupport our efforts to export agricultural products because \nglobally, that helps to reduce greenhouse gas emissions when \nyou look at global averages.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    It is similar to the policies that we have discussed in \nthis committee in regard to natural gas.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 4, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 75, 'start_offset': 32}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 96, 'start_offset': 81}}, 'display_name': 'PERCENT'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 117, 'start_offset': 110}}, 'display_name': 'NORP'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 156, 'start_offset': 148}}, 'display_name': 'NORP'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 166, 'start_offset': 161}}, 'display_name': 'NORP'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'U.S. natural gas, \naccording to the National Energy Technology Laboratories, is \nover 40 percent cleaner than Russian natural gas when supplied \nto European and Asian countries.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 25, 'start_offset': 21}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'So once again, using U.S. gas \nresults in lower greenhouse gas emissions globally.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Do we need to do a better job implementing best management \npractices and investing in R&D to ensure that we are maximizing \nopportunities with our farmers with agricultural lands?'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\nAbsolutely.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'To figure out how we do a better job enhancing \nsequestration and do it in a way that is complementary to the \nobjectives of our farming community.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 71, 'start_offset': 66}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    So with that, I am going to yield back, and thank you Madam \nChair.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 15, 'start_offset': 9}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Ms. Castor.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'All right.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 16, 'start_offset': 4}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 51, 'start_offset': 42}}, 'display_name': 'TIME'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Dr. Moore-Kucera, you are recognized \nfor 5 minutes.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 14, 'start_offset': 4}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n\n  STATEMENTS OF DR.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 21, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 52, 'start_offset': 44}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 62, 'start_offset': 54}}, 'display_name': 'NORP'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 89, 'start_offset': 79}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 167, 'start_offset': 163}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 175, 'start_offset': 170}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 179, 'start_offset': 177}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'JENNIFER MOORE-KUCERA, CLIMATE INITIATIVE \n DIRECTOR, AMERICAN FARMLAND TRUST; FRED YODER, CORD, SOYBEAN, \n   AND WHEAT FARMER, CO-CHAIR, SOLUTIONS FROM THE LAND; TINA \n OWENS, SR.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 8, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 29, 'start_offset': 10}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 84, 'start_offset': 74}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 147, 'start_offset': 139}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'DIRECTOR, AGRICULTURE FUNDING, AND COMMUNICATION, \n DANONE NORTH AMERICA; VIRAL AMIN, VICE PRESIDENT, COMMERCIAL \n         DEVELOPMENT AND STRATEGY, DTE ENERGY RESOURCES\n\n             STATEMENT OF DR.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 43, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'JENNIFER MOORE-KUCERA\n\n    Dr. Moore-Kucera.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 12, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 104, 'start_offset': 83}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 166, 'start_offset': 143}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Chair Castor, Ranking Member Graves, and \nhonorable members of the committee, I am Jennifer Moore-Kucera, \nthe Climate Initiative Director for American Farmland Trust.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 37, 'start_offset': 25}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'An \norganization founded 40 years ago to help protect farmland, \nadvance sound farming practices, and keep farmers on the land.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\nI thank you for the opportunity to testify and applaud the \ncommittee for exploring the critical issue of agriculture and \nclimate change.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n    Our nation's crop and ranch lands offer immediately \navailable, low cost, and proven ways to address climate change \nby sequestering carbon and reducing greenhouse gas emissions."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\nNo other option to combat climate change comes with more of the \nco-benefits we need for a sustainable future.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'It is imperative \nwe work across the political spectrum to make this opportunity \na reality.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Our farms and our futures depend upon it.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 12, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Climate change threatens lives, livelihoods, our food \nsecurity, and our economy, and is no longer a distant problem.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\nRecord high temperatures, drought, wildfires, storms, and \nfloods are becoming more intense and frequent.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Collectively, \nthese events negatively impact our crops, soil, and water.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 36, 'start_offset': 33}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'You \nare probably already seeing one of more of these impacts in \nyour own districts.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 32, 'start_offset': 22}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'As we speak, northern California is \nsuffering from intense wildfires in what has become a new \nnormal.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 16, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 103, 'start_offset': 70}}, 'display_name': 'QUANTITY'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Agriculture contributes to these challenges as a net \nemitter of more than 580 million metric tons of carbon dioxide \nequivalents per year.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'However, these emissions can be \nsubstantially reduced or even offset with continued adoption of \nwhat are commonly referred to as regenerative climate smart or \nsoil health practices.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 8, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Two proven low-cost soil health practices are cover crops \nand conservation tillage.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 21, 'start_offset': 17}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 59, 'start_offset': 55}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 101, 'start_offset': 91}}, 'display_name': 'PERCENT'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 158, 'start_offset': 147}}, 'display_name': 'PERCENT'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 229, 'start_offset': 199}}, 'display_name': 'QUANTITY'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 269, 'start_offset': 265}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 284, 'start_offset': 273}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 303, 'start_offset': 299}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Working with the USDA colleagues, we \nestimate that if U.S. farmers adopted cover crops on 25 percent \nof our cropland and conservation tillage on 100 percent of our \ntillable acres, we could reduce nearly 150 million metric tons \nof carbon dioxide equivalents per year or one quarter of the \ntotal U.S. agricultural emissions, and there are numerous other \npractices available that can further reduce these levels which \nwe can discuss during questions.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 8, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 78, 'start_offset': 74}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 105, 'start_offset': 101}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 246, 'start_offset': 235}}, 'display_name': 'PERCENT'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    AFT recently documented the co-benefits of soil health \npractices on four farms from across the U.S. After implementing \nnew soil practices, they found that in addition to reducing \ntheir greenhouse gas emissions by an average of 379 percent, \nthese same farms significantly cut nitrogen, phosphorus, and \nsediment losses and increased yields.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 9, 'start_offset': 4}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 69, 'start_offset': 67}}, 'display_name': 'MONEY'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'The three row crop \nfarmers increased their average net income by $42 per acre per \nyear.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    These gains, however, are not possible unless we keep \nfarmland as farmland.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 17, 'start_offset': 13}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 40, 'start_offset': 24}}, 'display_name': 'QUANTITY'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 108, 'start_offset': 104}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 117, 'start_offset': 113}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'According to USDA, over 25 million acres \nof farm and ranch land were converted to development between \n1982 and 2015.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Once land is lost to development, we lose the \nability to further sequester carbon, and the remaining lands \nare subject to increased pressures.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 68, 'start_offset': 65}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Encouraging agricultural \neasements and compact urban growth are two ways to protect \nfarmland while reducing transportation emissions.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 10, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Today I am here as a scientist, not as a policy expert.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 56, 'start_offset': 53}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\nNonetheless, I want to share some perspectives from AFT policy \nexperts.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 19, 'start_offset': 11}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'We call on Congress to seize the opportunities and \nmake agriculture a key partner in fighting climate change.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'This \ncould be achieved through a comprehensive climate bill or \nintegrated into a transformational farm bill.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 10, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 20, 'start_offset': 12}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 75, 'start_offset': 66}}, 'display_name': 'PRODUCT'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    First, Congress should expand upon the successful voluntary \nFarm Bill conservation programs.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Historically, these programs \nhave more demand than available funding.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 11, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 34, 'start_offset': 26}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 134, 'start_offset': 130}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 147, 'start_offset': 139}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Second, we encourage Congress to leverage other Federal \nprograms and State-level innovations such as the pilot programs \nin Iowa and Illinois that offer reductions on crop insurance \npremiums for cover crop adoption.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 10, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'ORDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Third, we need additional research on practices that help \naddress climate change and quantify their impacts.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'This \nknowledge will inform farmers and ensure good, sound public \ninvestments.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Lastly, we must find new ways to fund these practices and \nreward farmers for reducing greenhouse gases.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'This can include \nengaging consumers and private companies through environmental \nmarkets, supply chain management, and labels.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Producers are struggling to make ends meet.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Such efforts \nare models for encouraging best practices and keeping producers \nviable.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': "Our nation's farm and ranch lands have numerous \nscalable opportunities to address climate change with the co-\nbenefits we need for our future."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 9, 'start_offset': 6}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'We at AFT are excited to \ncontinue this conversation and serve as a resource as you move \nforward.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Thank you once again for the opportunity to testify.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 39, 'start_offset': 27}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 142, 'start_offset': 121}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 188, 'start_offset': 169}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 213, 'start_offset': 190}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 275, 'start_offset': 225}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 395, 'start_offset': 335}}, 'display_name': 'WORK_OF_ART'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 441, 'start_offset': 425}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 536, 'start_offset': 514}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n    [The statement of Dr. Moore-Kucera follows:]\n                               __________\n\n               Testimony of Jennifer Moore-Kucera, Ph.D.\n\n          Climate Initiative Director, American Farmland Trust\n\n   Before the U.S. House of Representatives Select Committee on the \n                             Climate Crisis\n\n      ``Solving the Climate Crisis: Opportunities in Agriculture''\n\n                            October 30, 2019\n\n    Chair Castor, Ranking Member Graves, and Honorable Members of the \nHouse Select Committee on the Climate Crisis."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 20, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 88, 'start_offset': 65}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'I am Jennifer Moore-\nKucera, the Climate Initiative Director for American Farmland Trust.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 52, 'start_offset': 40}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\nOur nonprofit organization was founded 40 years ago to help protect \nfarmland, advance sound farming practices, and keep farmers on the \nland.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    I thank you for the opportunity to testify and I applaud the \ncommittee for exploring the critical issue of agriculture and climate \nchange.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    I want to open by saying that addressing climate change by \npromoting climate-smart, regenerative agricultural practices can be a \nwin-win-win.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': "We can ensure our nation's food security, improve our \nenvironment, and enhance economic returns to farmers and ranchers."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 91, 'start_offset': 88}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\nMoreover, we already have the tools to reduce, or even eliminate, net \ngreenhouse gas (GHG) emissions, and scientists and farmers are coming \nup with new innovations all the time.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Along the way, we can make \nfarmers and ranchers more productive, more profitable, and more \nresilient to the ups and downs of weather and markets.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'And finally, all \nof society will reap numerous additional benefits, including cleaner \nwater, more wildlife habitat, and more productive soils that can keep \ngrowing food for generations to come.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Not many sectors of the economy \nhave the positive opportunities that we do in agriculture, so we need \nto work together, across the political spectrum, to seize these \nopportunities.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n                      climate risks to agriculture\n    There is a lot at stake.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Too often we think of climate change as an \nabstraction, something that will happen in the far-off future.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 16, 'start_offset': 9}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "But for \nAmerica's farmers and ranchers, climate change is already a daily \nreality."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Extreme weather events, including record high temperatures and \ndrought in parts of our country, threaten crop productivity, stress \nwater supplies, and increase wildfire risks, while more frequent and \nintense storms in other areas wash away the soil and increase flooding.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\nCollectively, these events negatively impact our crops and the soil and \nwater resources we depend on.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'They also threaten livestock, wildlife, \npeople, national food security, and our economy.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 34, 'start_offset': 12}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 58, 'start_offset': 56}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 95, 'start_offset': 92}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 101, 'start_offset': 97}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Within just the past 22 years, we have experienced 20 of the \nhottest years on record (WMO, 2019).'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Increased temperatures are \npredicted to impact crop yields and germination and harvest timing.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 101, 'start_offset': 80}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\nThese impacts may be positive or negative depending on the crop and \nlocation (Roesch-McNally et al.,'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 4, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '2019).'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 62, 'start_offset': 39}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Whereas some crops might \nbenefit from a longer growing season, the species and varieties of \ncrops grown in an area shift, resulting in the need for new equipment, \nknowledge, and resources to maintain viability.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Other impacts include \ngreater risks of disease, insect, and weed pressures due to higher \ntemperatures, longer growing seasons, and more frost-free days, which \nwill increase dependence on inputs such as fungicides, herbicides, and \ninsecticides.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    In addition to higher temperatures, more extreme weather events are \nprojected.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Some areas will experience increased duration, frequency, \nand intensity of drought, whereas other areas will be subjected to \nintense storms, leading to major flooding.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'So-called 500-year floods \nhave become 100-year floods.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 71, 'start_offset': 64}}, 'display_name': 'LOC'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 81, 'start_offset': 72}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 172, 'start_offset': 166}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 179, 'start_offset': 175}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'This makes planting and harvest more \ndifficult, as seen in the Midwest this year when unusually wet \nconditions led to one of the latest planting seasons on record (Rippey, \n2019).'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'These events also lead to soil loss from erosion and flooding of \nfarm fields, compounding water quality problems.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 193, 'start_offset': 175}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 209, 'start_offset': 195}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Other concerns, especially in western states, involve the reduction \nin snowpack amount and earlier peak flows (snow melt), which would \nreduce water availability during the growing season (Roesch-McNally et \nal.,'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 4, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '2019).'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Heavy and earlier spring rains or flood events will delay \nplanting or force farmers to perform field operations (e.g., tillage, \nplanting) when the soil is susceptible to compaction or erosion.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Major \nflooding also imperils infrastructures such as roads, railroads, barge \nlandings, and buildings necessary for storage and crop processing.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\nHigher temperatures and increased drought increase stress on both \nlivestock and crops, thus requiring greater inputs to maintain their \nhealth.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 34, 'start_offset': 31}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Increased carbon dioxide (CO2) levels will have both positive and \nnegative effects on agriculture.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Additional CO2 will \nstimulate growth in some crops, such as soybean and wheat, and may \nprovide some protection against moderate drought.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 24, 'start_offset': 21}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 109, 'start_offset': 104}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 115, 'start_offset': 111}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'However, increasing \nCO2 levels will also stimulate weed growth, potentially \nincreasing herbicide use (Ziska, 2003).'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 147, 'start_offset': 142}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'In addition, higher \nCO2 levels cause plants to take up less nutrients, leading \nto less nutritious feed in the trough and food on our plate (Myers et \nal.,'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 4, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '2014).'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Finally, drought and high temperatures will result in increased \nwildfire risk which threatens homes, fields, livestock, wildlife, and, \ntragically, human life.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Smoke damage for certain susceptible specialty \ncrops (e.g., wine grapes) has resulted in decreased quality and can \nnegatively affect farmers and farm workers exposed to unhealthy air \nconditions.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 7, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 50, 'start_offset': 40}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Farmers and their neighbors in northern California are \nsuffering from intense wildfires at the time of this testimony, in what \nhas unfortunately become a new normal.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Chances are that all of you are \nalready seeing one or more of these impacts within your own districts.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 134, 'start_offset': 131}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 166, 'start_offset': 149}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 170, 'start_offset': 168}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n                 agriculture's greenhouse gas emissions\n    Agricultural practices, in part, contribute to total greenhouse gas \n(GHG) emissions in the United States (US)."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 19, 'start_offset': 16}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 93, 'start_offset': 64}}, 'display_name': 'QUANTITY'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 176, 'start_offset': 160}}, 'display_name': 'PERCENT'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 188, 'start_offset': 186}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 205, 'start_offset': 200}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 211, 'start_offset': 207}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'The most recent EPA report \nindicates that agriculture releases about 582 million metric tons (MMT) \nof carbon dioxide equivalents (CO2e), which translates to \napproximately 9% of total US emissions (USEPA, 2019).'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 311, 'start_offset': 306}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 317, 'start_offset': 313}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\\1\\ In contrast \nto other production sectors, which are dominated by energy-related \nCO2 emission sources, the bulk of agriculture's impact on \nclimate change is due to nitrous oxide (N2O) and methane (CH4) \nemissions from fertilizer application, manure handling, and enteric \nfermentation from livestock (USEPA, 2019)."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 89, 'start_offset': 85}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 147, 'start_offset': 140}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 205, 'start_offset': 202}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n---------------------------------------------------------------------------\n    \\1\\ CO2e refers to the carbon dioxide equivalent, \nbecause methane (CH4) and nitrous oxide (N2O) are \nconverted to their CO2 equivalent, in terms of their global \nwarming potential.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 123, 'start_offset': 119}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 276, 'start_offset': 275}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 287, 'start_offset': 285}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 329, 'start_offset': 326}}, 'display_name': 'PERCENT'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 350, 'start_offset': 347}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n---------------------------------------------------------------------------\n    The following percentages exclude the 40.1 MMT CO2 from \nfuel combustion in agriculture to focus on the contribution of \nagricultural management as reported in the agriculture chapter (Chapter \n5) of the US EPA 2019 inventory report:\n           53% of agriculture's GHG contributions are in the \n        form of nitrous oxide (N2O) from agricultural soil management \n        (activities such as fertilizer application, growing N-fixing \n        plants), drainage of organic soils and irrigation practices, \n        manure management, and field burning of agricultural residues."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 62, 'start_offset': 47}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 89, 'start_offset': 79}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 145, 'start_offset': 142}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 151, 'start_offset': 147}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 157, 'start_offset': 153}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n        Nitrous oxide stays in the atmosphere about 114 years and is \n        almost 300 times more efficient at trapping heat than \n        CO2 (IPCC, 2007).'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 15, 'start_offset': 12}}, 'display_name': 'PERCENT'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n           46% of agricultural emissions are from methane (CH4) \n        primarily from enteric fermentation from livestock and manure \n        management, as well as rice cultivation and field burning of \n        agricultural residues.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 7, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 62, 'start_offset': 49}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 76, 'start_offset': 74}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 132, 'start_offset': 129}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 161, 'start_offset': 157}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 167, 'start_offset': 163}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "Methane's lifetime in the atmosphere is \n        only 12 years, but it is 25 times more efficient at trapping \n        heat than CO2 over a 100-year period (IPCC, 2007)."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 43, 'start_offset': 34}}, 'display_name': 'PERCENT'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 64, 'start_offset': 61}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 111, 'start_offset': 97}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 116, 'start_offset': 113}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n           Unlike other sectors, only 1.5% of agriculture's GHG \n        contributions are from Carbon Dioxide (CO2), predominantly from \n        urea fertilization and liming."}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 111, 'start_offset': 108}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "\n                   agriculture as a climate solution\n    Although agriculture currently is a net source of GHG emissions, \nfarmers and ranchers can be some of our nation's greatest allies in \nfighting climate change."}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'There are numerous crop land and grazing land \nmanagement practices that are known to increase the amount of carbon \nplants can capture and ultimately store belowground in the soil.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'This \nprocess is called soil carbon sequestration.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 29, 'start_offset': 26}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 44, 'start_offset': 41}}, 'display_name': 'FAC'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 71, 'start_offset': 70}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 123, 'start_offset': 119}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 130, 'start_offset': 126}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    In fact, soils store 2-3 times more CO2 than the \natmosphere and 2-5 times more C than that stored in vegetation (IPCC, \n2013).'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 45, 'start_offset': 15}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 89, 'start_offset': 77}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 172, 'start_offset': 169}}, 'display_name': 'PERSON'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Unfortunately, between the late 1880s to 1985, agricultural \nsoils have lost half or more of the soil organic carbon (SOC) that was \npresent prior to industrialization (Lal, 2004).'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 10, 'start_offset': 6}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Since 1985, increased \nyields, reduced tillage intensity, and improved genetics have resulted \nin many soils beginning to increase soil carbon levels, and there is \nmuch more we can do!'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 32, 'start_offset': 5}}, 'display_name': 'QUANTITY'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 64, 'start_offset': 62}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'With more than 900 million acres of agricultural \nland in the US, we have an enormous opportunity to rebuild soil organic \ncarbon, sequester atmospheric carbon, and reduce N2O and \nCH4 emissions as well.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 159, 'start_offset': 157}}, 'display_name': 'GPE'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 214, 'start_offset': 203}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 239, 'start_offset': 218}}, 'display_name': 'QUANTITY'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 270, 'start_offset': 262}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Some estimates suggest that if we \nwere able to adequately address economic, social, and technical \nbarriers to implementing best soil management practices, US croplands \nhave the potential to sequester 1.5 billion to 5 billion metric tons of \nCO2e per year for 20 years (Sanderman et al.,'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 19, 'start_offset': 6}}, 'display_name': 'FAC'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '2017; Zomer et \nal.,'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 4, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '2017).'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Moreover, the same agronomic practices that increase carbon \nsequestration also help to mitigate flood events, protect water \nquality, recharge groundwater, and increase resilience to drought \n(Lehman et.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 8, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'al, 2015).'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Rebuilding soil health is crucial to sustaining agriculture, \nenhancing the profitability of farmers and ranchers, and combatting \nclimate change.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 69, 'start_offset': 26}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': "Soil health is defined by USDA-Natural Resource \nConservation Service (NRCS) as ``the continued capacity of a soil to \nfunction as a vital living ecosystem that sustains plants, animals, and \nhumans.''"}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 45, 'start_offset': 44}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 203, 'start_offset': 202}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 303, 'start_offset': 302}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 427, 'start_offset': 426}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 531, 'start_offset': 530}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 719, 'start_offset': 718}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 839, 'start_offset': 838}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'Healthy, high-functioning soils:\n          (1) Produce food, fuel, fiber, and medicinal products using \n        management strategies that maintain or enhance environmental \n        quality;\n          (2) Store, filter, and release water, and thus protect or \n        improve water quality;\n          (3) Are resilient to environmental disturbances such as \n        drought, fire, floods, and temperature extremes;\n          (4) Resist diseases, pests, and pathogens, thus reducing the \n        reliance on pesticides;\n          (5) Store and cycle nutrients internally, reducing the \n        reliance on external inputs and the potential for off-site \n        movement of nutrients into the air and water;\n          (6) Store and cycle carbon and modify other greenhouse gases, \n        helping to reduce climate change; and,\n          (7) Maintain biodiversity and habitat, which is critical to \n        all above functions.'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 49, 'start_offset': 19}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 67, 'start_offset': 63}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 250, 'start_offset': 247}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 276, 'start_offset': 262}}, 'display_name': 'ORG'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    Recently, the USDA-NRCS Soil Health Division has outlined four soil \nhealth principles to improve soil function for a variety of ecosystem \noutcomes, but they also apply to building resilient agricultural \nsystems that sequester C and reduce GHG emissions (Roesch-McNally et \nal.,'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 4, 'start_offset': 0}}, 'display_name': 'DATE'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': '2019).'}}
{'annotations': [{'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 8, 'start_offset': 4}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 37, 'start_offset': 36}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 208, 'start_offset': 207}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 329, 'start_offset': 328}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 587, 'start_offset': 586}}, 'display_name': 'CARDINAL'}, {'text_extraction': {'text_segment': {'end_offset': 670, 'start_offset': 669}}, 'display_name': 'MONEY'}], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'The four principles are:\n          (1) Minimize disturbance (typically physical disturbance is \n        the major focus, with a target to reduce tillage depth, \n        intensity, and frequency);\n          (2) Maximize soil cover, often through mulching, reduced \n        tillage, residue retention, and cover crops;\n          (3) Maximize the continuous presence of roots, which is \n        typically achieved through cover crop planting but also longer \n        rotations, forage, and biomass plantings, and incorporation of \n        perennial crops into the rotation; and\n          (4) Maximize biodiversity through practices similar as those \n        described in #3; but can also include the integration of \n        livestock into the cropping system and diversifying cover crop \n        mix or more diversified crop rotations.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': '\n    In addition to sequestering carbon, healthy soils absorb more water \nduring heavy rains, which reduces runoff.'}}
{'annotations': [], 'text_snippet': {'content': 'They also offer better \nresilience during periods of drought because the land holds more water.'}}
